hey everybody welcome to this into
English using practical video
you can use this video the practical
listening and comprehension and ice peak
for started remember the subscribed
to a channel
click on the bell and followers on instagram
you save sorry d and the talk about for
July
the for the goliath Americans
independence day and the extremely
important for many your brand and the soul at
first but the meaning behind the fourth
of July and why Americans care plus deet
the 13 American colony is the kindergarten
independence of a blind on July for
17 seventy-six Mrs Lynde Venus document
with declaration of independence
was boring and that we declaration of
independence
designed by some very famous Americans
such as John Hancock
Thomas Jefferson Benjamin Franklin is
mine and mediators arranger the founding
fathers
and America during this time the American
colony for finding the revolutionary
Boer and art criticism finally and 17th 3
more and this in a merry go with free
from British school and Mary Consolata
celebrating the fourth of July
speaker system peppers and Frieda
with  This historical import, and for the
world,
to the guys, the Declaration of
Independence inspired many other people
in other countries to fight for their
freedom. This usually happened
on Independence Day or National Day. But
I understood CMS Americans for July.
This is the stocking. Most people in other
countries are super edgy, Marc. By many, you
notice and serve patriotic.
Is this my level? A critical one. The
portal July is the ultimate, Peter. Yes, I
did.
In the US, in the Americans, the perfect
opportunity to celebrate their country
and chauffeur patriots. And okay, well,
let's talk about some of the
traditions. The Americans have fun. The
most beautiful portal for July is the mini American flag.
The stone-colored American flag is
everywhere on people's streets. Slow, but
you'll see life. Someone here
in the US memoranda for the Fourth of July.
Okay, and another tradition is having a BBQ
with family and friends on this day. One
American and barbecues in Syria,
outside—in someone's backyard—through the
park at the Gate of Light.
People have barbecues everywhere, and most
people spend time outside. The most
common typhoon is the barbecue on this day:
hamburgers.  and hotdogs on course
ilovebeads is specially winter freshets
the grill house the lightning hamburgers
and hotdogs so santing elst and medium
arrogance those countries photo that is code
beach and never do the beach to
celebrate with my family
18 dozen with whom is there always my
sports and other games
am and my apple watch the fireworks
this is the most iconic before you lite
edition
you can see fireworks all around you
found for parts of the city thunder
firewatch over really impressive it already
super of the watchtime with your family and
friends
that will for the they leave a comment and
tell me your country national day and
remember the subscribed to a channel
click on the bell and followers on instagram
for more english
fitz and lizzie as an external
[Music]
[Applause]